tv-tube.tv 2016-12-17

# Privacy policy | TvTube - TV channels on the Internet, live or video clips, on any device, anywhere

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us by our [contact form](http://www.tv-tube.org/informations/contact). 

At TvTube, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information that is received and collected by TvTube and how it is used. 

Log Files
     Like many other Web sites, TvTube makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider (ISP), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user's movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable. 
Cookies and Web Beacons

TvTube uses cookies to store information about visitors preferences, channel selections, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser or components. 

Some of our advertising partners may use cookies and web beacons on our site to further track users consumptive patterns across our site, as well as other third party sites utilizing their services. 

Advertisements

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to display advertisements and links that appear on TvTube. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies (such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and/or to personalize the advertising content that you see. 

We utilize the [DoubleClick cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/dart_adserving.aspx) to help advertisers and publishers manage and serve ads on TvTube and other Google adsense powered sites. Advertisers may serve ads based on interests associated with non-personally identifiable online activity, such as videos viewed, frequency of uploading or activity on other AdSense partner sites. Advertisers may also serve ads to you based on previous activity on that advertiser's website. This non-personally identifiable information is held separately from your TvTube Account data, or other personally identifying information in our possession. 

You may at any time view, add, edit to the interest categories used to provide you with relevant advertisements by using the [Ads Preference Manager](http://www.google.com/ads/preferences?hl=en-US) for the DoubleClick cookie. Your preferences will be adjusted and respected across TvTube, and all other Google Adsense DoubleClick affiliated sites. For more information regarding interest-based advertising, pleasee see the Ad Preference Manager [FAQ](http://www.google.com/privacy_faq.html). 

You may also may choose to [opt out of the DoubleClick cookie](http://optout.doubleclick.com/cgi-bin/optoutgoogle.pl) at any time. If you opt-out, ads delivered to your browser by our ad-serving technology will not be served based on the DoubleClick cookie. Find more information on [Google Privacy Center](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html) about opting out of the DoubleClick cookie.

We use “Google Analytics” to collect information about use of this site. Google Analytics collects information such as how often users visit this site, what pages they visit when they do so, and what other sites they used prior to coming to this site. We use the information we get from Google Analytics only to improve this site. Google Analytics collects only the IP address assigned to you on the date you visit this site, rather than your name or other identifying information. We do not combine the information collected through the use of Google Analytics with personally identifiable information. Although Google Analytics plants a permanent cookie on your web browser to identify you as a unique user the next time you visit this site, the cookie cannot be used by anyone but Google. Google’s ability to use and share information collected by Google Analytics about your visits to this site is restricted by the Google Analytics Terms of Use (as amended for government websites) and the Google Privacy Policy. You can prevent Google Analytics from recognizing you on return visits to this site by disabling cookies on your browser. 

Google Analytics employs cookies to define user sessions, which allows for the collection of data about how visitors are using the websites. Google Analytics uses only first-party cookies for data analysis. This means that the cookies are linked to a specific website domain, and Google Analytics will only use that cookie data for statistical analysis related to your browsing behavior on that specific website. According to Google, the data collected cannot be altered or retrieved by services from other domains. 

We use the Google Analytics Advertising Features such as "Google Analytics Demographics and Interest Reporting". By using the Advertising Features, we have enable Google Analytics to collect data about site traffic via Google advertising cookies and identifiers, in addition to data collected through a standard Google Analytics implementation. 

If you choose, you can opt out by turning off cookies in the preferences settings in your web browser. 

TvTube does not provide or disclose any personal information to third-party companies or ad-servers, without your consent. You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. TvTube's privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.
